Lola Hopper collection, Inclusive: 1965-2013, undated, Bulk: 1971-1977, 2008, undated
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
Lola Hopper collection
Inclusive: 1965-2013, undated, Bulk: 1971-1977, 2008, undated
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
51
Hopper, Lola
4 document boxes and 14 oversized boxes.
The Lola Hopper collection houses various materials collected by longtime Texas political activist Lola Hopper. Ranging from the 1960's to 2013, the collection consists primarily of campaign materials and items from Hopper’s trip to the 2008 Democratic National Convention as a delegate. There are also various physical artifacts from the Texas Capitol building during renovations, and papers, photographs, and items from Hopper’s time as secretary for Texas Representative and Senator Donald G. Adams.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Excellent.
Biography/Profile
Lola Hopper was born near Houston and grew up there before moving to San Marcos prior to the start of high school. She was involved in high school student government, introducing a bill to desegregate extracurricular activities such as sports. The bill passed and sports were desegregated after she graduated. Hopper attributes her love for politics to the success of this early effort.
Hopper studied English and history at Austin Community College for one year before leaving school in 1965 to work as a secretary for Terrell Blodgett, Administrative Assistant to Texas Governor John B. Connally. In 1969, she became the office manager for Donald Adams, working for Adams during his time as a State Representative and a State Senator. When Adams left office in 1978, Hopper took a job in the TXU lobbying office until 1987 when she became office manager for State Senator Judith Zaffirini for two years. In the 1990’s, Hopper worked for Texas Attorney General Jim Mattox in his Outreach for the Blind Project, then for Attorney General Dan Morales’ Child Support Division. Finally, she worked for Texas Mental Health and Mental Retardation in Austin.
After a lengthy career working for various politicians and political organizations, Hopper retired in 2002. However, she remained an active volunteer for various Democratic Party politicians and political causes. Most notably, she was an early volunteer for the Hillary Clinton 2008 Presidential Campaign, coordinating volunteers when Clinton visited Waco on the campaign trail and recruiting veterans to attend the event. She was so active in Clinton’s campaign that she was chosen as a delegate to attend the 2008 Democratic National Convention in Denver, Colorado, casting her vote for Clinton in the race eventually won by Barack Obama.
Scope and Content
The papers and materials collected by Lola Hopper were donated to the Baylor Collections of Political Materials in the summer of 2012. The collection contains mostly campaign materials from various campaigns Lola Hopper supported over 50 years of political activity, including yard signs, T-shirts, bumper stickers, and a large collection of political buttons. Also included are a large number of photographs taken at various occasions.
Hopper worked as a secretary for Texas State Senator Donald G. Adams during the 1970's. The materials in this collection include letters from Adams and his wife Linda, some office materials, photographs of Adams and his staff, and newspaper clippings. The collection also includes several items related to the State of Texas honoring Donald Adams as Governor for a Day on October 15, 1977. This includes several photographs, some certificates and commendations, stationary and programs, clippings, coffee cups, and the gavel and block which “Governor” Adams used that day.
Hopper collected several artifacts from various renovations of the Texas Capitol Building, starting in the 1960's and continuing all the way to the 1980's. These artifacts include bricks, chunks of masonry, nails, and a light fixture. The stones and bricks have had one side covered in felt so that the artifacts can be displayed, and Hopper kept them out of a respect for their historical value.
Arrangement
Prior to reprocessing, items in this collection were loosely organized by topic. Since being reprocessed in 2020, the items have been sorted topically into five series: I. Texas Capitol Renovation, II. Donald Adams, III. Campaigns, IV. 2008 Presidential Campaign, and V. Personal.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 51. Acquired 2012-06-26
Related Resources
Items in related collections
Donald G. Adams Papers, Inclusive: 1962-1980, undated, Bulk: 1972-1977, undated
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Clinton, Hillary Rodham; Edwards, Chet, 1951-
Subjects (Organizations)
Democratic National Committee (U.S.).; Democratic Party (U.S.); Texas -- Legislature.; Texas. Legislature. Senate.
Places
Texas -- Politics and government -- 1951-
Subjects
Democratic National Convention (2008: Denver, Colo.).; Elections -- Texas.; Legislators -- Texas.; Political campaigns -- Texas.; Political candidates -- Texas.; Political participation -- Women -- Texas.; Politicians -- Texas.; Women -- Political activity -- Texas.
Genres
Advertisements.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Photographs.; Realia.; Souvenirs (Keepsakes)
- Texas Capitol Renovation, 1967-1986, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  Series I. Texas Capitol Renovation contains materials Lola Hopper collected during various Texas Capitol Building renovations between the 1960's and 1980's. Hopper personally took photographs during some of the renovations, including pictures inside the inner walls of the dome and pictures of the statue of the Goddess of Liberty when the statue was removed from the top of the dome. Hopper also collected several pieces of masonry from inside the Capitol building, including limestone, granite, marble, floor tiles, nails, and light fixtures. All of these three-dimensional materials are in their own separate box, mostly wrapped in foam for protection. The three-dimensional materials in this collection are in good condition, whereas the photographs are slightly faded and are in average condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Photographic print
  - Photographs of inner walls of Capitol, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photographs from Goddess of Liberty statue replacement, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Limestone brick with nails, undated (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - 5 original floor tiles from Texas Capitol, undated (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Inner wall limestone signed by John Connally, 1967 (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Limestone brick taken from inner walls, 1967 (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Chunk of marble with seal commemorating 64th Legislature/Texas Sesquicentennial, undated (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Granite block, undated (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Nails taken from walls, undated (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Part of light used in top of Capitol Building, just below the Lady, undated (Box 5 OVZ, Folder 8)
- Donald Adams, 1971-1977, undated; 2
  Series II. Donald Adams contains materials related to Lola Hopper’s time as secretary for Texas State Representative and State Senator Donald Adams. Hopper kept many pictures of Adams, his staff, and his time in office, as well as letters and notes from Adams and his wife Linda, newspaper clippings, and stationery from the Texas Constitutional Convention. Hopper also collected a lot of material from Donald Adams’s Governor for a Day ceremony in 1977. This includes coffee cups, a gavel, booklets, newspaper clippings, and photographs. The folders are organized chronologically, with documents first and photographs second. The three-dimensional materials are housed in a separate box. The materials in this series are in good condition.
  - Office materials, 1971-1977, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Letters/Notes from Donald Adams, 1971-1977, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Letters/Notes from Linda Adams, 1972-1977, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Campaign materials, 1972, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1973-1977, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Thank You notes, 1973-1977, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Texas Constitutional Convention, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Valentine’s Day office cartoon, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - SR 462, Honoring State Senate Secretaries, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Clippings about Donald Adams Governor for a Day ceremony, Legislative Clipping Service, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Invitations for Governor for a Day ceremony, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - “Donald Adams: Governor of Texas” booklet, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Thank You notes for Governor for a Day ceremony, 1977, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Stationery and napkins from Governor for a Day ceremony, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Federal Government directory, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Photograph, State Representative Clyde Haynes, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Photograph, Autographed photo of Donald Adams, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Photographs, Photos at the Texas House, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Photographs, Donald Adams’s Birthday Party, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Photographs, Autographed photo of Donald Adams and staff before swearing in ceremony to State Senate, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Photograph, Lola Hopper in Donald Adams’s Office, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Photographs, Presiding over Texas Senate, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Photographs, Governor for a Day ceremony, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Photograph, Children eating cake, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Photograph, Donald and Linda Adams, 1971-1975 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Photograph, Donald Adams at his seat in the Senate Chamber, 1971-1975 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Photograph, Donald Adams being presented a gift by his staff, 1971 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Photograph, Donald Adams’s staff, 1973 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Photograph, Donald Adams and his Senate staff, 1973 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Photograph, Donald Adams addressing high school students, 1973 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Photograph, Donald Adams’s staff with Elsworth Greer, 1975 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Photograph, Donald, Linda, and Donny Adams with Donny’s school class, 1975 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Photograph, Donald Adams addressing high school students from his district, 1975 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Photograph, Donald Adams and staff, 1977 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Photograph, Staff on last night of legislative session, 1977 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Photograph, Last night of legislative session, 1977 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Certificate of Commendation for Service, Governor for a Day ceremony, 1977 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Donald Adams and Lola Hopper, undated (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Etched paperweight, Sixty-Fourth Legislature, 1975 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Two coffee mugs from Governor for a Day ceremony, 1977 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Gavel and block from Governor for a Day ceremony, 1977 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 3)
- Campaigns, 1984-2013, undated; 3
  Series III. Campaigns contains a wide variety of materials Lola Hopper collected during her time volunteering for and supporting political campaigns. Hopper vigorously supported the Democratic Party in Texas and nationwide, and this series holds many campaign materials she collected from local, state, and federal elections. She was also active in many non-electoral political causes, including denuclearization and women’s issues. Her collection of campaign material includes campaign buttons, bumper stickers, yard signs, printed material, and photographs. Among the three-dimensional materials in this collection are t-shirts and hats with candidates’ names and messages printed on them. The materials in folders are sorted by candidate’s last name when a candidate is mentioned, and alphabetically when a specific candidate is not named. Most of the materials in this collection are in good condition although some of the buttons are slightly rusty.
  - Baird, “Re-Elect Judge Baird Texas Court of Criminal Appeals” sticker, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Belew, “Elect Jay Belew in '92” campaign pin, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bell, Happy New Year card from the Bells (Alison, Chris, Atlee (12) & Connally (11)), undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Cantrell, “Re-Elect Cantrell County Commissioner” button, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Carter, “Re-Elect Carter/Mondale” button, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Clinton, “Bill Clinton for President” bumper stickers, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Clinton, “Clinton/Gore” button, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Clinton, “92 Clinton/Gore” button, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Edwards, “Chet Edwards Congress” yard sign, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Edwards, “Vets for Chet” yard sign, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Edwards, “Chet Edwards Congress” stickers, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Edwards, “I’m a Chet Fan” fan, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Edwards, “Chet Edwards for Congress” bumper sticker, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Edwards, “Chet Edwards Congress” bumper stickers, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Edwards, “Republicans for Chet Edwards” bumper sticker, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Edwards, “Vets for Chet” bumper sticker, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Edwards, “Ags for Edwards” bumper sticker, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Edwards, Photo of group including Chet Edwards and Lola Hopper, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Edwards, Christmas cards from Chet Edwards, 2004-2013, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Edwards, Chet Edwards campaign literature, 2006-2007, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Emley, “Dave Emley for Waco City Council” nail files, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Evans, “Elect Cindy Evans” sticker, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Gassaway, “Re-Elect Judge Mike Gassaway” pin, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Hoelscher, “Elect Ann Hoelscher for County Commission — Pct. 4” advertisement, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Layman, “Elect Joe Layman Democrat” advertising booklet, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Logue O’Herren, “Katherine Logue O’Herren for Justice” advertising booklet, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mayfield, “Elect Alan Mayfield Judge” pamphlet, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - McGovern, “McGovern” button, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Mondale, “Democrats Let’s Send Ronnie and Phil the same message we sent Bill” button, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Mondale, Photographs, Mondale-Ferraro Rally, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Murphey, Campaign materials for Sam Murphey, stickers, flyer, yard sign, 2008, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Noriega, “Rick Noriega for U.S. Senate” buttons, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Pickle, Pickle shaped pin with “Jake” on it, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Richards, Ann Richards buttons, 1991-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Seley, “Wimp Seley for District Judge” thimble, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Turner, Yard signs for Chris Turner, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Turner, “Chris Turner for State Representative” bumper stickers, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Turner, “Chris Turner for State Representative” stickers, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Turner, Campaign pamphlet, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Turner, “I’m a Chris Turner Fan” fan, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - “The 11th National Conference on Women and the Law” button, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 1994 Texas Democratic Convention name tag (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - “Better active today than radioactive tomorrow” button, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - “Don’t Yell at me: I’m a volunteer” button, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - “Had enough? Vote Democrat” stickers, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - “I [Heart] Waco” button, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - “I Like Ike” button, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - “Is There Life After Law School?” button, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Button, Laughing male politician, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - “Question Authority” button, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - “Read my Lipstick: I’m Voting Democrat” Emily’s List bumper sticker, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - “Texas Democrat” button, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - “Texas Democratic Women” button, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - “Texas Farm Workers Union” button, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - “Try the Rapist, not the Victim” button, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - “Turn TX Blue” bumper sticker, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - “United Steel Workers” bumper sticker, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - “Vote Democrat” button, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - “Who Killed Karen Silkwood?” button, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - “Women Against Nukes” button, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Pin, Yellow dog & “Democrat” on blue Texas, red, white, and blue ribbon, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Photograph, Autographed Photo of Dan Morales with Lola Hopper, 1993 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Photograph, Autographed Photo of Keith Oakley with Lola Hopper, 1993 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - “Chet Edwards Congress” t-shirt, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - “Chet Edwards: He’s Working for Us” t-shirt, undated (Box 8 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - “Sylvia Garcia for Texas Senate” t-shirt, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - “Wendy Davis Texas Senator District 10” t-shirt, undated (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - “Sam Murphey for State Representative, District 55” t-shirt, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - 2 “Chris Turner for State Representative” t-shirts, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - “Re-Elect Judge Mike Gassaway” t-shirt, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - “I hunted with Dick Cheney” and bullet holes t-shirt, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - “Baylor Democrats: Jesus didn’t ride in on an elephantEL” t-shirt, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - “Elect JW Duke Justice of the Peace” baseball cap, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Doll, George W. Bush with cowboy hat and boots, pants on fire, undated (Box 12 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - “America 2000 The Democratic Convention” tote bag (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 5)
- 2008 Presidential Campaign, 2008, undated; 4
  General condition: Excellent.
  Series IV. 2008 Presidential Campaign contains materials belonging to Lola Hopper from the 2008 election, mostly from the Democratic primary process. Hopper was an enthusiastic supporter of Hillary Clinton for the Democratic nomination and collected a significant amount of Clinton campaign materials. Hopper was eventually chosen as a delegate for the State of Texas to the Democratic National Convention where she supported Clinton. Barack Obama ultimately emerged as the party's nominee.
  This series contains many materials from Hopper’s trip to Denver, Colorado for the convention, including tee shirts, programs, bags, backpacks, and the hat adorned with buttons that she wore on the convention floor. The series is organized alphabetically, with the Hillary Clinton materials first and the Democratic National Convention materials afterwards. The series is in excellent condition.
  - “Bring back Bill & Hillary Clinton” button, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, Chelsea Clinton at rally, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - “Conversation with America” buttons, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - “Hillary” button, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - “Hillary Clinton 2008” button (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Hillary Clinton campaign stickers, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Photograph, Hillary Clinton speech, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - “Hillary for President” bumper sticker, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - “Hillary for President” buttons, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - “Hillary for President” hand signs, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - “Hillary for President” yard sign, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - “In it to Win it” buttons, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - “Senator Clinton: Champion for New York” booklet, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Letters from Hillary Clinton, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Clippings from Conventions, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - “Democratic National Convention” bicycle pin, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Democratic National Convention official program, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Democratic National Convention shopping guide, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Denver 2008 swipe card (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - “Emily’s List Celebrates the Power of Democratic Women”, pamphlet, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Photograph, J. D. Steinhle at speech at Convention Center, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - “Moving Texas Forward” button, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Name tags at convention, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Official 2008 Democratic National Convention visitor’s guide (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Planning binder for trip to 2008 Democratic National Convention in Denver (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Printouts of pictures of Lola Hopper at the 2008 Democratic National Convention (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - “Texas Democrat” bumper stickers, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - “[Texas] Democrat” bumper sticker, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Hat with campaign buttons worn to the 2008 Democratic National Convention, undated (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Two flags, a USA flag and Texas flag, taken to 2008 Democratic National Convention, undated (Box 13 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - “Deep in our Hearts: Hillary Clinton Texas National Convention 2008” t-shirt (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - “Democratic National Convention, Denver Colorado” backpack, 2008 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - “08 DNCC” tote bag, 2008 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - “Texas Democratic Party Moving Texas Forward” tote bag, 2008 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Panoramic photograph of Texas delegation to Democratic National Convention 2008 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 4)
- Personal, 1965-1990, undated; 5
  Series V. Personal contains materials which are not related to Lola Hopper’s political activities. This includes coffee cups, photographs, patriotic clothing and bumper stickers, Texas-themed items, and a Mother’s Day card. The series is organized alphabetically by subject. Overall, the materials are in good condition.
  - Photographs, The Alamo, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - “Born to Boss” bumper sticker, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Photograph, Capitol Building, Austin, Texas, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Certificate of Thanks from Texas Attorney General, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Coin, University of Texas Football, Cartoon Longhorn on front, Schedule on back, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Eradicate Mental Illness mailer from cast of television show “House”, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Materials from visit to William J. Clinton Presidential Center, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Photographs, Reception for Secretary of State John Hill, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Texas bumper stickers, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Photographs, Texas Capitol on a snowy day, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - “Vote Mom!” Mother’s Day card and button, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - “The Women’s Movement” by Fannie Lou Spelce, Print, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - “LOLA” coffee mug, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Texas Sesquicentennial coffee mug, 1981 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Paperweight, Appointment to the American Airlines Fair Ladies, 1967 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - “Senate Staff — 1986 Texas Sesquicentennial” sweatshirt (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Star Spangled Banner shirt, undated (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 1)